If you use a natural nail tip, you're actually going to need to blend the artificial tip in with the natural nail.
With that, you'll just take your drill or your regular nail file if you don't have an electric one, and just kind of go over the tip itself just to blend it in with the natural nail.
You're not actually going to rough up the nail anymore.
You're just going to blend it in.
On the French tip, you don't do that because it's already got the nice smile line and you don't need it blended any.
Again, this is just for the natural tip.
And again, if you don't have an electric nail file, you can do the same thing with a regular nail file.
You just want to blend the tip, such as this, and even though it's going to be on the nail itself, you're not going to file the actual nail, you're just filing the tip.
And you just want to blend it all the way from one side to the other.
And that is how you blend the natural nail tip with the natural nail.